ILGWU Research Department Records 5780/168
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Community Council of Greater NY, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Preliminary Statement of a Proposed Study of the Integration of Newcomers to New York City in the Post-War Decade, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
    By Dr. Odin W. Anderson. May 13, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Copy of Most Recent Study, "Fee Charging for Adoption, Child Placement and Maternity Shelter Care", Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
    By Lazare Teper. January 21, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Enclosed Copy of New Pamphlet, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
    By Walter Mankoff. September 11, 1956. Item is in English.
- Teper, Lazare. Correspondence, N, 1956-1958, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Copies of Statement Made Before Department of Commerce, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. November 3, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Self-Explanatory Letter, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By B.H. Lerner. June 19, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Copy, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Robert R. Richmond. April 18, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Blouse Production Statistics, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. September 10, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Tables on Production of Various Items of Women's Apparel, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Walter Mankoff. September 20, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Table Showing Annual Production of Women's Skirts for the Year 1947-1955, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. September 17, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Copy of Telegram Sent To All Fifteen members of Senate Finance Committee, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By B.H. Lerner. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Negotiations between Government and Japanese Government, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Erwin Feldman. January 5, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Copy of Letter Submitted to the Department of Commerce in Connection with the Japanese Importation of Cotton Dresses, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Erwin Feldman. August 27, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Letter to Mr. Mantler, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. October 6, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Promotional Issue and Charter Subscription Blank for the New Publication, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Alfred Baker Lewis. November 19, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Data reported by the U.S. Bureau of the Census on the Output of Unit-priced Dresses, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. May 10, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Letter Regarding the Copy of the Robert Nathan Associates Report, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Sidney S. Korzenik. May 7, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Letterto Mr. Kolesnikoff, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Sidney S. Korzenik. June 29, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Letter to Mr. Weiss, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Sidney S. Korzenik. May 1, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Copy of Letter on April 16th to the Wage and Hour Division, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Sidney S. Korzenik. April 26, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Letter about Copy of Letter to the Wage and Hour Division, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. April 18, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Letter about Copy of Letter Regarding the Learner Certificate, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. April 9, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Letter about Copy of Letter Written to Mr. Milton Brooke, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Sidney S. Korzenik. Feburary 14, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Letter Enclosing Copy of Objection to the Learner Certificate to Glamourette Fashion Mills, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. February 9, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Letter Regarding List of Employer Associations, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Sidney S. Korzenik. May 20, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Letter of December 12, 1956, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By James A. Ryan. January 9, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Thank you letter to Mr. Cook, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. June 14, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Registration for Conference on "Research and Development and Its Impact on the Economy", Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Alan T. Waterman. March 20, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Acknowledgment of Letter Regarding Research Activities, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. August 26, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Acknowledgement of Note Sent by Charles Abrams, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. January 28, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Summary of the Discussion at the Lunchon-Meeting of the Research Division of the New School, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lewis Lorwin. December 14, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Acknowledgement of December 4th Note, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. December 5, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Acknowledgement of Note of May 31, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 30: Letter with Prospectus of Study: New York Metropolitan Region Study Prospectus, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Martin Segal. November 23, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Letter Regarding Copy of the Draft of Locational Study of the Women's and Children's Apparel Industries, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Roy B. Helfgott. August 1, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Reminder of Meetings to Attend on August 26 and 27, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Raymond Vernon. July 24, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Acceptance of Invitation for Rainwear Dinner, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. May 28, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Invitation to Dinner and Rainwear Fasion Show, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Simon Cohen. June 11, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Copy of General Executive Board Report Enclosed, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. May 25, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Letter Regarding Dr. Lubin's Paper, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. March 12, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Letter with Comments on the Paper Presented by Dr. Isador Lubin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. January 30, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Letter about Copy of Paper on Minimum Labor Standards in Underdeveloped Countries, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Daniel Nelson. January 23, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Letter about People Able to Speak on the Subject of Labor Union Activity, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By Lazare Teper. October 14, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Letter to Dr. Nourse, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Teper, Lazare. Correspondence, P, 1955-1958, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Letter to Research Director of I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By John A. Patton. January 10, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Order Fixing Place Of Hearing, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By George S. March 20, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Letter to Lazare Teper, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By Ruth W. Ayres. February 14, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Thank-you for the Copy of "Conditions in the Women's Garment Industry", Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By E.S. Roscoe. June 28, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Letter Enclosed with Copies of Contracts and Extract from 1957 Mid-Year Report, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By Lazare Teper. September 3, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Inter-Office Communication with Thermofax Copy of an Item on "Hawaii Fashion Week", Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By Lazare Teper. August 20, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Thank-you for Report to the Board, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By Thomas B. Newton. January 19, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Letter Regarding Latest Report, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By Lazare Teper. Janaury 15, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Letter Regarding Room Reservation for Income Conference, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By Lazare Teper. February 8, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Letter Regarding Meeting on May 25th, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By Alfred Politz. May 20, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Invitation to Meeting on May 25th, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By Alfred Politz. May 9, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Summary Sheet Outlining Research Program, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By Dewey Anderson. December 8, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Copy of Questionnaire, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    January 28, 1958. Item is in English.
- Teper, Lazare. Correspondence, J, 1956-1957, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Correspondence of Japanese Federation of Textile Industry Workers' Unions and I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    By Minoru Takita. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Letter Regarding News of Restriction on Sale of Japanese Textile Goods, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    By Minoru Takita. April 18 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Letter Regarding View on Effectiveness of Program, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    By W.G. Cochran. June 27, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Predict Census Will Show City's Population Is Up, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    By R.E. Johnson. September 20 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Proposal, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    By Bess Alpiner. September 11, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Corrected Galleys of Article "BLS Consumers", Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    By Lazare Teper. March 28, 1956. Item is in English.
- National Bureau of Economic Research, 1955-1958, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Copies of Papers Delivered at the Conference, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Copy of 1956 Convention Proceedings, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By Lazare Teper. August 8, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Copies of National Bureau's 38th Annual Report, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By William J. Carson. July 8, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Request for 39th Annual Report of the National Bureau Copies, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By Lazare Teper. July 7, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Copy of Letter to Mr. Dubinsky, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By William J. Carson. January 29, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Answer to February 24 Letter Returning Galley Proofs of Paper, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By Mary C. Wing. June 25, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Copy of Leter to Mr. Dubinsky Inviting Support by I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By William J. Carson. November 29, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: List of Papers Presented At the Conference, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By Lazare Teper. November 22, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Letter Regarding Work of National Accounts Review Committee, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Mimeographed Note Regarding Data on Membership, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By Lazare Teper. August 20, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Manuscript with Corrections of Corrections, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By Lazare Teper. July 1, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Letter of May 24th with Enclosure of Mr. Garvy's Introcution and Table of Contents of Volume 23 of the Studies in Income and Wealth, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By Lazare Teper. May 27, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Western Union Sending Blank: Review, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By Lazare Teper. June 7, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Letter about April 5th and 6th, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By Lazare Teper. November 30, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Copies of Comments on Miller's Paper, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By Lazare Teper. May 1, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Letter about Next Meeting of Conference on March 23 and 24, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By George Jaszi. January 27, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Letter to Mr. Dubinsky, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By William J. Carson. September 7, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Acknowledgement of Letter of August 23, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By Lazare Teper. August 26, 1955. Item is in English.
- Teper, Lazare. Correspondence, K, 1955-1957, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Acknowledement of Inquiry on Union affiliations of the Marjorie Montgomery Dress Company, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    By Lazare Teper. July 27, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Copy of Teichler-Curtiss-Wright Decision, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    By Lazare Teper. July 5, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Re: UC Cases, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    By Lazare Teper. January 25, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Thank-you Letter for Sending Files, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    By Lazare Teper. March 9, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Letter Asking for Records of Unemployment Insurance Compensation Cases, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    By Lazare Teper. February 16, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Copy of Reply Received from Secretary of Labor Mitchell re Glover vs. Simmons, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    By Sol D. Kapelsohn. August 22, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Letter to Chief of Benefits, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    By Sol D. Kapelsohn. June 28, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Letter Regarding Minimum Wages of Industries Engaged in Interstate Commerce, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    By Melvin Kleblatt. April 7, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Comments on Saul Nelson's Proposed Letter to Mayor Wagner, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    July 6, 1956. Item is in English.
- New York State AFL-CIO, 1955-1958; Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Letter of Appreciation to Delegates and Affiliated Organizations, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Ray Corbett and Harold C. Hanover. July 15, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Letter to Everett Friedman, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daniel Nelson. April 23, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Letter about the I.L.G.W.U. Research Department's Summary of the New York Unemployment Insurance Law, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Everett M. Friedman. April 21, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Letter Enclosed with Excerpts from Laws of all Eight States, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daniel Nelson. March 31, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Letter Enclosed with Copy of Decision Reported in Volume 13, #2 of the Workmen's Compensation Board's Decisions, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daniel Nelson. March 18, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Inter-Office Communication: Re: Telephone Conversation, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Seymour Bernstein. January 9, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Letter Enclosed with Summaries of Statistics of Cases Handled, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Lazare Teper. April 17, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Letter Enclosed with Two Clippins from the New York Times, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daniel Nelson. April 3, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Thank-you for Letter of May 22nd, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Harold C. Hanover. May 23, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Letter Enclosed with List of Suggestions Made Regarding Desirable Amendments in Field of Social Insurance, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daniel Nelson. July 10, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Letter of Congratulations, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daniel Nelson. May 22, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Letter of Appreciation of Officers and Executive Council, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Harold C. Hanover. March 8, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Letter Enclosed with Memorandum, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daneil Nelson and Lazare Teper. March 18, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Letter Regarding Copy of Release of 1957 Legislative Program, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Lazare Teper. February 4, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Enclosed Tables on Benefit Rate, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daniel Nelson. February 1, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Inter-Office Communication: Appeal Board Decisions, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daniel Nelson. December 11, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Proposals of the New York State Republican Legislative Program for 1957, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Harold C. Hanover. Janaury 30, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Labor's Evaluation of the 1957 Republican Legislative Program As Published for Workmen's Compensation, Unemployment Insurance, and Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Thomas A. Murray and Harold C. Hanover. January 25, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Letter Enclosed with Copy of the State Federation of Labor's Evaluation of the 1957 Republican Legislative Program for Workmen's Compensation, Unemployment Insurance and Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Everett Friedman. January 30, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Letter Enclosed with Three Tables Showing Maximum Benefits Rates, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Lazare Teper and Daniel Nelson. January 15, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Letter Enclosed with Rate Schedule Raising Maximum Unemployment Insurance Benefit, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daniel Nelson. December 21, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Request for Three Copies of Hanover's Report, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daniel Nelson. September 24, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Fournier Case, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Daniel Nelson. September 19, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Response to Lazare Teper, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Harold C. Hanover. January 31, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Letter of Appreciation to Harold Hanover, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: Letter Enclosed with Bill for Book, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Dan Nelson. January 13, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Letter Regarding the Letter Nelson Cruikshank Wrote, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Everett Friedman. October 28, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Letter Regarding Participation in Regional Conference, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Everett Friedman. October 25, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Information for Officers, Delegates and Organizations Who Introduced Proposed Legislation at Our 92nd Annual Convention, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Harold C. Hanover. October 25, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Division Plans to Make "Non-representated Cases" a Permanent Procedure, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Everett Friedman. October 4, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Letter Enclosed with Memorandum, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Item 32: Conference of Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By H.C.H. September 12, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Letter Regarding Memorandum in Robern Shoe Manufacturing Case, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Harold C. Hanover. August 19, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Letter About Memorandum Submitted on Behalf of the New York State Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Lazare Teper and Everett Friedman. August 12, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Letter Enclosed with Summary of New York Unemployment Insurance Law, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Lazare Teper and Everett Friedman. August 5, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Letter Regarding to Belated Payments to Claimants in Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Harold C. Hanover. July 29, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Letter About Paper on Non-Represented Cases in the Adjudication, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Harold C. Hanover. April 20, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Proposed Letter To Industrial Commissioner Lubin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By Lazare Teper. February 1, 1955. Item is in English.
- Teper, Lazare. Correspondence, MC, 1958, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Cooperation in a Study of Long-Term Collective Bargaining Agreements, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Jack Stieber. September 30, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Letter About New Material Sent to Include in Files for the International Ladies Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By John W. Riegel. January 23, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Letter Regarding Reprint of Article on Price Indices, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Fred H. Blum. October 22, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Thank-you Letter for Final Version of Fred Blum's Paper, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Lazare Teper. December 26, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Letter Regarding Letter from Public Administration Service, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Walter Mankoff. October 1, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Acknowledgement of June 29 Letter, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Lazare Teper. June 30, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Acknowledgement of Letter of July 24, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Lazare Teper. August 18, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Letter Regarding Study Dealing with improvement of Working Conditions in Industry, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Sidney A. Whitt. June 25, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Letter Regarding Abstract, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Acknowledgement of Receipt of Copy of Survey of the Apparel Manufacturing Industry for 1955, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Walter Mankoff. March 12, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Acknowledgement of Letter of July 4th Regarding Alcoholism in Industry, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Lazare Teper. July 9, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Letter About Economic Hokum Sweepstakes, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    December 24, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Letter About Internal Memo, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Lazare Teper. December 16, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: LetterAbout Set of Correlations Suggested by Mr. James Lever, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Lazare Teper. September 23, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Letter about 1949 Edition of Study Notes for the Society's Examinations, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Item 16: Letter with Copy of Note to Mr. Schnitzler, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Lazare Teper. January 24, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Letter to Julia L. Maietta, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Lazare Teper. October 10, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Letter Regarding Desire to Institute a Trade Union Section in College Library, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Lazare Teper. June 23, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Acknowledgement of Letter Regarding Supplier of Women's Coveralls, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Walter Mankoff. March 27, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Letter of Statements That Do Not Appear In Compliance In Various Respects, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Kenneth A. Meiklejohn. July 2, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Letter Regarding Memorandum on Constitutionality of the Present FISA Provisions, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)